jayshetty.me 2018-12-22

# Privacy - Jay Shetty

This Privacy Policy was modified on May 25, 2018 and enters into effect immediately.

Jay Shetty’s Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by us anytime you interact with Jay Shetty, such as when you visit one of our websites, when you purchase our products and services, or when you call our sales or support associates. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at Jay Shetty and we go to great lengths to protect it.

By providing personal information to us or through our websites, you understand and consen to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to all countries and territories. Please read the following privacy policy before

using this website or providing any personally identifiable information through this website. It will be assumed that if you provide us with any personally identifiable information that you have read and understand this policy.

Some portions of this privacy policy may not apply to information that you provide voluntarily, or that we may obtain, through means other than our websites, such as, but not limited to, telephone, postal mail, other live and print media, and other available public information sources. Our websites are intended for users who are located internationally.   This privacy policy is part of the Jay Shetty website terms and conditions which governs your use of this website in general.

**Why We Collect Personal Information**

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

**What Information We Collect and How We May Use It**

There are a number of situations in which your personal information may help us give you better products. For example: phone with an associate. When you interact with Jay Shetty, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences; your credit card information and other information. We also collect information for market research purposes – such as your occupation and where you use your computer – to gain a better understanding of our customers and thus provide more valuable service. We collect information regarding customer activities on our websites. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our websites, products, and Internet services are of most interest to them. We may use personal information to provide products that you have requested as well as for auditing, research, and analysis to improve Jay Shetty’s products. We collect personal information about users of our websites through activities such as purchase transactions and completion of forms on our websites. Such information is collected when users register or subscribe to accounts or features on our websites, make online purchases, complete surveys, comment on our blogs, opt-in to our email marketing list, submit a comment or question to us using a “contact us” form or similar feature, send us an e-mail, or in any other way submit personal information voluntarily to us through our websites.

If you post blog comments, use a bulletin board, chat room or other similar features on our website you should be aware that any information you share is visible to other users. Personally identifiable information you submit to one of these forums can be read, collected, or used by other individuals to send you unsolicited messages. Jay Shetty is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. For example, if you choose to make information, which was previously non-public, available by enabling certain user features, Jay Shetty will collect that information from your interaction and the information will become publicly available.

**When We Disclose Your Information**

Jay Shetty takes your privacy very seriously. Jay Shetty does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers. Except as otherwise disclosed to you, we will not sell, rent or disclose your personal information to third parties without notifying you of our intent to share the personal information in advance and giving you an opportunity to prevent your personal information from being shared.

Within Jay Shetty To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with legal entities within the Jay Shetty group globally who will take steps to safeguard it in accordance with Jay Shetty’s privacy policy. Jay Shetty will use your personal information to respond to your requests and to provide you with our product and service offerings. We may also use your personal information to maintain our internal record keeping. We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both personal information and website usage information, and use such information along with information obtained

from other sources, including third parties. In addition, we may send you notices (for example, in the form of e-mails, mailings, and the like, such as our e-newsletters), and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies and events sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you. You may opt out of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions in the right to opt in and optout section below. We may analyze user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our websites and e-mails, both on an  individual basis and in the aggregate.

**How We Protect Your Personal Information**

Jay Shetty takes precautions – including administrative, technical, and physical measures – to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. The Jay Shetty websites use secure encryption, provided by a third party, on some web pages where credit card information is required.

**Integrity of Your Personal Information**

Jay Shetty has safeguards in place to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date for the purposes for which it is used. Naturally, you always have the right to access and correct the personal information you have provided. And you can request a copy of your personal information, your product registration history, and your interactions with our sales and support agents by contacting us.

While Jay Shetty strives to protect the security and integrity of sensitive personal information provided through this website, due to the inherent nature of the internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee 100% that information during transmission through the internet or while stored in our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others.

If you contact us by e-mail or a “contact us” form or similar feature on our website, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit. Do not send sensitive information (such as payment card information, social security numbers, employer identification numbers, passwords, or pin numbers) to us via e-mail or via a “contact us” form or similar feature on our website. We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission. In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your personal information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. You consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification.

**Cookies and Other Technologies**

As is standard practice on many websites, the Jay Shetty websites use cookies, third  party software, and other technologies to track anonymous user data to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. We also use cookies and other technologies to make sure that our online advertising is bringing customers to our products and services. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our websites, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. We also use cookies to customize

your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us.

Information such as your country and language helps us provide a more useful online shopping experience. And your contact information, product serial numbers, and information about your computer helps us register your products, personalize and set up your internet service and provide you with customer service.

If, however, you prefer not to enable cookies you can disable cookies in your browser. Please note that certain features of the Jay Shetty websites will not be available once cookies are disabled.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click-stream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Jay Shetty will not use the information collected to market directly to a specific person.

**Right to Opt-In and Opt-Out**

You may have the right to “opt in” and “opt out” of certain uses of your personal information. For example, at the time you are requested to provide personal information on any of our websites, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to receive correspondence from us. You may opt out of any email marketing communications with Jay Shetty by clicking the opt-out link in our messages, or by sending an email to us stating that you would like to be removed from a specific marketing list, or all communications entirely. Please note that you cannot unsubscribe or opt-out from certain correspondence from us, including messages relating to your account transactions. You may be contacted by Jay Shetty in connection with your relationship to us as a client, or as follow up.
